(
"ai_sub_version": "3.0.2",
"generated_at": "2026-06-24T00:34:56.157824",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援OKです
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is OK.
紙細工の花びらを
Paper-crafted flower petals
ある人は美しいとぼやいた
Someone muttered were beautiful
この地球の横顔は
This Earth's profile
どう見えてる？キミの世界では
How does it look? In your world
現実を逆さまにして
Turning reality upside down
失くしそうなモノだけ振り落とした ah
I shook off only the things I was about to lose, ah
手のひらで拾い上げようとしたら
When I tried to pick them up in my palm
指の隙間すり抜け消えてった
They slipped through the gaps in my fingers and disappeared
“形あるものだけが
"Things with form are not
すべてじゃないけど
Everything, but
形あるものが
I want things with form
どうしても欲しいよ”
No matter what"
この世界を (da-ra-da)
This world (da-ra-da)
変えることは (la-la-la-la)
Changing it (la-la-la-la)
きっとできないけど (da-ra-da)
I surely cannot (da-ra-da)
キミの中の世界なら変えられるはず
But the world inside you, I should be able to change
芽吹いて 咲いて 実って 枯れて
Sprouting, blooming, bearing fruit, withering
何ひとつ欠かせないから (da-ra-da-da)
Because none of it can be missing (da-ra-da-da)
最後にキミが笑ってくれれば
If in the end you smile for me
もうそれだけでいい
That alone is enough
言葉の綾を紡ぐ人 優しさを編む人
People who weave the nuances of words, people who knit kindness
それぞれの正義を解ってあげたい
I want to understand each other's justice
絡まった矛盾と辻褄合わせ
Tangled contradictions and making ends meet
そんな刹那を抱え今日を生きてる
Holding onto such moments, I live today
分け合った灯り 隣から隣へ
The shared light, from neighbor to neighbor
やがてひとつに 夜の帳へ
Eventually becoming one, beyond the veil of night
息を吹き込んだ
I breathed life into it
キミとじゃなきゃだめなんだ ah
It has to be with you, ah
このまま寝てしまうには
To fall asleep just like this
もったいないほど
Too precious to waste
優しさに包まった
Wrapped in kindness
夜だった
It was a night
はっきり浮かび上がった 夢の輪郭
The clearly emerged outline of a dream
それは確かに愛だった
That was certainly love
ツキが見守る今夜 そっと一瞬を抱き締めた
Tonight, watched over by the moon, I gently embraced the moment
煌めく星 ooh
A twinkling star ooh
色や形 温度や意味
Color and shape, temperature and meaning
まるで何もかも違うボクらだけど
Although we are completely different
きっと最後には
Surely in the end
この音で繋がってる
We are connected by this sound
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援OKです
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is OK.
紙細工の花びらを
Paper-crafted flower petals
ある人は美しいとぼやいた
Someone muttered were beautiful
この地球の横顔は
This Earth's profile
どう見えてる？キミの世界では
How does it look? In your world
現実を逆さまにして
Turning reality upside down
失くしそうなモノだけ振り落とした ah
I shook off only the things I was about to lose, ah
手のひらで拾い上げようとしたら
When I tried to pick them up in my palm
指の隙間すり抜け消えてった
They slipped through the gaps in my fingers and disappeared
“形あるものだけが
"Things with form are not
すべてじゃないけど
Everything, but
形あるものが
I want things with form
どうしても欲しいよ”
No matter what"
アニメにハマって 歌いたくなっちゃった
I got so into anime, I just had to sing!
推しのシーン見ながら カラオケ歌えるなんて
Singing karaoke while watching my favorite scenes...
尊すぎてツラい！
It's so precious, it hurts!
歌いたい曲見つけよう！
Let's find the songs you want to sing!
ジョイサウンド！
JOYSOUND!
ReGLOSS 2nd Album「Snapshot」のレコードとカセットテープが、2026年2月25日よりHMV限定で発売決定しました！
The vinyl and cassette tape of ReGLOSS's 2nd Album "Snapshot" are confirmed to be released exclusively at HMV starting February 25, 2026!
12月17日いっぱいまでに御予約頂くと、期間限定予約特典としてスマホサイズステッカーをプレゼント！
If you pre-order by December 17th, you will receive a smartphone-sized sticker as a limited-time pre-order bonus!
さらに抽選で5名様に、サイン入りポスターをプレゼント！
Plus, 5 lucky winners will receive a signed poster by lottery!
HMV、ReGLOSS、レコード、カセットで検索！
Search for HMV, ReGLOSS, record, cassette!
以上！
That's all!
ReGLOSSでした〜！！
We are ReGLOSS!!
紙細工の花びらを
A paper petal...
ある人は美しいとぼやいた
...someone murmured was beautiful.
この地球の横顔は
How does the profile of this Earth...
どう見えてる？キミの世界では
...look to you in your world?
現実を逆さまにして
Turning reality upside down,
失くしそうなモノだけ振り落とした ah
I shook off only the things I seemed to lose, ah.
手のひらで拾い上げようとしたら
When I tried to scoop them up in my palm,
指の隙間すり抜け消えてった
they slipped through my fingers and disappeared.
“形あるものだけが
"Tangible things...
すべてじゃないけど
...aren't everything,
形あるものが
but still, tangible things...
どうしても欲しいよ”
...are what I desperately want."
この世界を (da-ra-da)
Changing this world... (da-ra-da)
変えることは (la-la-la-la)
...is surely impossible, (la-la-la-la)
きっとできないけど (da-ra-da)
but I'm sure (da-ra-da)
キミの中の世界なら変えられるはず
the world inside of you can be changed.
芽吹いて咲いて実って枯れて
Budding, blooming, bearing fruit, and withering,
何ひとつ欠かせないから (da-ra-da-da)
because not a single thing is dispensable. (da-ra-da-da)
最後にキミが笑ってくれれば
If you smile in the end,
もうそれだけでいい
then that's all I need.
言葉の綾を紡ぐ人
Those who spin figures of speech,
優しさを編む人
those who knit kindness,
それぞれの正義を
I want to understand...
解ってあげたい
...each of their justices.
絡まった矛盾と
Holding onto tangled contradictions...
辻褄合わせ
...and trying to make things consistent,
そんな刹那を抱え
embracing such fleeting moments,
今日を生きてる
we live today.
分け合った灯り
The light we shared,
隣から隣へ
from one to the next,
やがてひとつに
soon becoming one,
夜の帳へ
into the veil of night.
息を吹き込んだ
I breathed life into it,
キミとじゃなきゃだめなんだ ah
it has to be with you, ah.
このまま寝てしまうには
It's too much of a waste...
もったいないほど
...to just fall asleep like this.
優しさに包まった
It was a night...
夜だった
...wrapped in kindness.
はっきり浮かび上がった夢の輪郭
The outline of the dream emerged clearly,
それは確かに愛だった
it was surely love.
ツキが見守る今夜
Tonight, watched over by the moon,
そっと一瞬を抱き締めた
I gently embraced this moment.
煌めく星
Sparkling stars,
色や形温度や意味
colors, shapes, temperatures, and meanings.
まるで何もかも違うボクらだけど
Although we are completely different in every way,
きっと最後にはこの音で繋がってる
I'm sure in the end we are connected by this sound.
この世界を (da-ra-da)
Changing this world... (da-ra-da)
変えることは (la-la-la-la)
...is surely impossible, (la-la-la-la)
きっとできないけど (da-ra-da)
but I'm sure (da-ra-da)
キミの中の世界なら変えられるはず
the world inside of you can be changed.
芽吹いて咲いて実って枯れて
Budding, blooming, bearing fruit, and withering,
何ひとつ欠かせないから (da-ra-da-da)
because not a single thing is dispensable. (da-ra-da-da)
最後にキミが笑ってくれれば
If you smile in the end,
もうそれだけでいい
then that's all I need.
I'll always be by your side
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
演出の都合上、照明の明滅にご注意ください / 声出し応援OKです
Please be aware of flashing lights / Cheering loudly is OK.
本日は、ReGLOSS 1st Live「Flashpoint」にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming to ReGLOSS 1st Live "Flashpoint" today!
Reach the top! We are...
いくぞー！
Let's go!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内させていただきます。
In order for you to enjoy the concert to the end, we have a few announcements.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
Recording, photographing, or using video recording devices during the performance is strictly prohibited.
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は、無理をせず近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
In the unlikely event that you feel unwell, please do not push yourself and let a nearby staff member know.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、大きく飛び跳ねる、ステージにものを...
Moshing, diving, jumping high inside the venue, throwing things on the stage...
大丈夫、大丈夫。
It's okay, it's okay.
緊張してる、緊張してる、緊張してます！すいません！
I'm nervous, I'm nervous, I'm so nervous! I'm sorry!
もう一回いきます！お客さんの声もあるからね。
I'll do it one more time! We have the crowd's support too.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、大きく飛び跳ねる、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、他のみんなの迷惑になったり、公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね！
Moshing, diving, jumping high inside the venue, throwing things on the stage, or any action that causes a nuisance to others or disrupts the performance is strictly prohibited. Please follow the rules and enjoy!
また！
And also!
また、本公演は映像配信及び写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合がございます。
Also, this performance will have cameras inside the venue for video broadcasting and photography, and the audience seats may be captured.
映像や写真はプロモーション等に使用される可能性がございますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
Please note in advance that the footage and photos may be used for promotions and other purposes.
ライブのハッシュタグは、「リグロスファーストライブ」です！ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてくだい！
The hashtag for this live is "#ReGLOSS1stLive"! Please use the hashtag and cheer us on!
それでは、開演までもう少々。
Now, there is only a little time left until the show starts.
盛り上がる準備はできてますか？
Are you ready to get excited?
みんなで一緒に盛り上がる！
Let's all get excited together!
以上、ReGLOSSでした！
That was ReGLOSS!
常識蹴っ飛ばして Wake up, people
Kick common sense away, wake up, people!
A to Z 蹴っ飛ばして 計画 計画 実行
Kick A to Z away, plan, plan, and execute!
どんなに小さくても 釘付け Pretty girl
No matter how small, nailed down, pretty girl.
一人じゃ足りない この声 響かせ S.O.S. call
Resonating this voice that isn't enough alone, S.O.S. call!
歌うたう君と 私の鼓動はシンパシー
You singing and my heartbeat are in sympathy.
いつのまにかそばにいるけれど 妙におもしろいパレード
You're by my side before I know it, a strangely interesting parade.
胸躍る 巡り合いは 一期一会...
A heart-dancing encounter is once-in-a-lifetime.
1 2 3で 変わってく この世界で
With a 1, 2, 3, changing in this world...
ちょっとつまづかないように 全部光らせて 包み込もう
...let's light up everything and wrap it up so we don't stumble a bit.
移ろう色褪せるように
As if shifting and fading away,
万全だったのかな
was it fully perfect?
秘密のオフレコ
A secret off-the-record...
春が来た パッパッパッとサクラ咲いて
Spring has come, cherry blossoms bloom suddenly!
泣かないで 笑って A to Z
Don't cry, smile from A to Z!
踊ってみて Summer アルゴリズムの中
Try dancing in Summer, inside the algorithm.
ショートで旅して 酔いが醒めるまで
Traveling with short videos until the buzz fades away.
サクラ咲いて
Cherry blossoms bloom,
踊ってみて Summer_
try dancing in Summer,
アルゴリズムの中
inside the algorithm,
ショートで旅して
traveling with short videos,
酔いが醒めるまで
until the buzz fades away.
カタチあるものに惑わされないように
So as not to be misled by things with form,
新しい今日
a new today.
変わってく世界を見つめてたのは
The one who was gazing at the changing world
きっと君じゃないけど
surely wasn't you, but...
君の中の世界なら 変えられるはず
If it's the world inside you, it should be changeable.
目一杯咲いてみせて 枯れて...
Show me blooming to the fullest, then withering,
誰一人 独りじゃないから
because not a single person is alone.
最後に君が 笑ってくれれば
If you smile in the end,
もう それだけでいい
that alone is enough.
Otonose Kanade
Kanade Otonose
Ichijou Ririka
Ririka Ichijou
Juufuutei Raden
Raden Juufuutei
Todoroki Hajime
Hajime Todoroki
Flashpoint - ReGLOSS 1st Live
なぁ...
Hey...
紙細工の花びらを
Paper-craft petals...
ある人は美しいとぼやいた
...someone grumbled that they were beautiful.
この地球の横顔は
This profile of the Earth...
どう見えてる？キミの世界では
...how does it look in your world?
現実を逆さまにして
Turning reality upside down...
失くしそうなモノだけ振り落とした ah
...I shook off only the things I was about to lose, ah.
手のひらで拾い上げようとしたら
When I tried to pick them up with my palm...
指の隙間すり抜け消えてった
...they slipped through my fingers and vanished.
“形あるものだけが
“Things with a physical form...
すべてじゃないけど
...aren't everything, but...
形あるものが
...things with form...
どうしても欲しいよ”
...I really, truly want them.”
この世界を
This world...
変えることは
...is something I certainly can't change...
きっとできないけど
...but surely...
キミの中の世界なら変えられるはず
...I should be able to change the world inside you.
芽吹いて咲いて実って枯れて
Sprouting, blooming, bearing fruit, and withering...
何ひとつ欠かせないから
...because not a single one of those moments can be missing.
飛び乗ってフューチャー
Jump on into the future!
フライングしたって オールライト Mr. Spotlight
Even if you jump the gun, it's alright, Mr. Spotlight!
ときめいてしまえば
If you just feel the excitement,
瞬く間に広がる解放区
a liberated zone will spread in the blink of an eye.
ひとつひとつ全てがパノラマ
Each and every thing is a panorama.
交われば満たされて Mr. Spotlight
Once we cross paths, we're fulfilled, Mr. Spotlight!
代わる代わる彩るパノラマ
Changing colors paint the panorama.
満ち溢れるフィーリングでしょ
It's an overflowing feeling, isn't it?
始まりの その時が来た
The moment of beginning has arrived.
Nothing's impossible
目覚ましが響いてから数回
A few times after the alarm clock rings,
この先はまだ誰も知らない世界
ahead lies a world that no one knows yet.
ボタン押してるだけじゃつまんない
Just pressing buttons is boring.
リアルタイムで通じ合って
Let's connect in real-time.
不意にかけるモーション
Unintentionally starting to move,
あとの祭りでも I don't mind
even if it's too late, I don't mind.
ドラマチックなシチュエーション
A dramatic situation.
行けるところまで行ってみたい
I want to go as far as I can.
選択肢にない Girl, let's go far away
It's not an option, girl, let's go far away.
届くように声を鳴らして
Make your voice ring so it reaches.
肌を貫くような真っ直ぐな痛みが
Even if a straight pain that pierces through your skin
伴っても
comes with it,
この仲間たちと最果てまで
with these companions, to the very end,
Keep running to the end
飛び乗ってフューチャー
Jump on into the future!
フライングしたって オールライト Mr. Spotlight
Even if you jump the gun, it's alright, Mr. Spotlight!
ときめいてしまえば
If you just feel the excitement,
瞬く間に広がる解放区
a liberated zone will spread in the blink of an eye.
ひとつひとつ全てがパノラマ
Each and every thing is a panorama.
交われば満たされて Mr. Spotlight
Once we cross paths, we're fulfilled, Mr. Spotlight!
代わる代わる彩るパノラマ
Changing colors paint the panorama.
満ち溢れるフィーリングでしょ
It's an overflowing feeling, isn't it?
飛び出せ ニューメディア
Leap out, new media!
恐れるものはない Mr. Spotlight
There is nothing to fear, Mr. Spotlight!
引き寄せなサイケデリック
Draw in the psychedelic,
透明な明日を変えて
let's change the transparent tomorrow
行こう
and go.
Mr. Spotlight
皆さん、こんにちはー！
Hello, everyone!
こんにちはー！
Hello!
ReGLOSS 3Dライブにお越しくださいまして、ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much for coming to the ReGLOSS 3D Live!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
本日は皆さん、楽しんでいって、素敵な一夜にいたしましょう！
Everyone, please have fun today, and let's make it a wonderful night!
お次は、あのナンバーをお届けいたします！盛り上がっていきましょう！
Next, we'll deliver that number! Let's get hyped!
みんな！次の曲は「Easy Breezy」だよ！
Everyone! The next song is "Easy Breezy"!
盛り上がる準備はいいですかー？
Are you ready to get hyped?
みんなで楽しんでいってね！
Hope everyone enjoys it!
Oki Doki! Easy Breezy!
とりあえずお近づきの
For now, let's get closer
Easy Breezy
大体いつもフェイバリット
mostly always my favorite.
Oki Doki! Easy Breezy!
このまままにまにいたいよね
This way, I want to stay as is, right?
Easy Breezy
踊ろうよエブリバディ
Let's dance, everybody!
それぞれ重ねて価値
Layering each other, we have value,
好むの好みそれそれぞれよ
what we like is up to each of us.
揃えば無敵になっちゃう
If we're all together, we become invincible,
そう決まりはない
that's right, there are no rules.
ゼロから始まって
Starting from zero,
愉快な仲間が集まればパフォーマー
when fun friends gather, we become performers.
無茶苦茶なストーリーも愛おしい
Even a crazy story is lovely.
一発かますわ
I'm gonna pull off something big!
Oh baby 今日も大体
Oh baby, today is mostly
伝染してゆく喜怒哀楽
our emotions are contagious.
分かち合える愛しい
It's lovely that we can share them.
共に行こう そう Reach the top, yeah!
Let's go together, yes, Reach the top, yeah!
絶対絶対絶対絶対駆け抜け中
Absolutely, absolutely running through right now,
今は自由気ままにフリースタイル
now, it's a free-spirited freestyle.
イタズラなユニバース
A mischievous universe,
実り実り実り実り実を落とすシナプス
synapses blooming, blooming, blooming and bearing fruit.
限界突破
Breaking through limits,
引き寄せるミラクル
drawing in a miracle.
みんなー！ペンライトよく見えてますよー！
Everyone! We can see your penlights really well!
まだまだドンドンブンブン振っていけ！
Keep waving them more and more!
Oki Doki! Easy Breezy!
とりあえずお近づきの
For now, let's get closer
Easy Breezy
大体いつもフェイバリット
mostly always my favorite.
Oki Doki! Easy Breezy!
このまままにまにいたいよね
This way, I want to stay as is, right?
Easy Breezy
踊ろうよエブリバディ
Let's dance, everybody!
ひとりつまんないなら私と踊りましょ
If you're bored alone, dance with me.
愛だ恋だとかいつも
Is love and romance always
片隅のものなのかな？つなぐプロット
something in the corner? A connecting plot.
楽しい時間はあっという間！そう！みんなとのライブだ！
Time flew by so fast when we were having fun! Yes! It's our live show with everyone!
いくぞー！
Let's go!
そう、かけがえないメモリーズ　握りしめりゃポジティブ
Yes, if I hold onto these irreplaceable memories, I'll stay positive.
運命　強気で行こう
Let's face our destiny with confidence.
全然平気って　言っとくね　あ、痛っ！
I'll tell you I'm totally fine—ah, ouch!
立ち上がれるエンパシー
Empathy that lets us rise up,
たまに目立つ傷は...
and the occasionally noticeable scars are...
Reach to the top, yeah!
絶対　絶対　絶対　絶対的な切符をチョイス
Absolutely, absolutely, absolutely, choosing the ultimate ticket.
今はもう自由気ままのミズイラズ
Now it's just us, free and easy.
Rollin' Rollin' Rollin' ロールしていくドロップス
Rollin' Rollin' Rollin', rolling like drops.
限界突破に　ひきつけろミラクル
Break past your limits and attract a miracle!
Okey Dokey, Okey Dokey, 予想最高のDays
Okey Dokey, Okey Dokey, the best days I imagined,
Easy Breezy, 大体いつでもFavorite
Easy Breezy, pretty much always our favorite.
Okey Dokey, Okey Dokey, このままでいいよね
Okey Dokey, Okey Dokey, in this moment, let's go,
Easy Breezy, 踊ろうよ Everybody
Easy Breezy, let's dance, everybody!
ReGLOSS 1st Live、
ReGLOSS 1st Live,
Flash×Pointへようこそ！
Welcome to Flash Point!
いつもの挨拶から行きましょう！
Let's start with our usual greeting!
Reach to the top, we are...
ReGLOSS!
では、さっそく自己紹介からしていきたいと思います！
Now, let's get right into our self-introductions!
はいはいはい！奏からやりたい！奏からやる！
Yes yes yes! I want to go first! Kanade will start!
どうぞどうぞ！
Go ahead, go ahead!
はーい！お待たせしました！みんなのアイドル、ちびっこ歌姫、音乃瀬奏こと、
Hi! Thanks for waiting! Everyone's idol, the tiny diva, Otonose Kanade,
たまごトーストだーい好き、音乃瀬奏です！
and major lover of egg toast, is here!
みんな、会いに来てくれて、黄色にしてくれてありがとう！
Thank you all for coming to see me and filling the venue with yellow!
そして！
And next!
可愛い、ポジティブ、ジーニアス、一条莉々華こと、一条莉々華だよ！
Cute, positive, genius, Ichijou Ririka, also known as Ichijou Ririka, is here!
やばい、もうみんなの声めっちゃ、この熱気、浴びてる、今！
Oh my god, I'm totally bathing in everyone's voices and this heat right now!
めっちゃ嬉しい！ありがとう！
I'm so incredibly happy! Thank you!
最高な気分！そして！
I feel amazing! And next!
はい、えー、ホロライブデバイス、ReGLOSSの賑やかしネタ枠担当、重度の活字中毒、学芸員資格を持つ、落語見習い、儒烏風亭らでんでございます！
Hello! From hololive DEV_IS, ReGLOSS's lively comedic relief, severe reading addict, curator license holder, and rakugo apprentice, Juufuutei Raden!
本日もどうぞよろしくお願い申し上げます。
I look forward to today, thank you very much.
最後は！
And last!
はい、ぷんぷんぷん！降って湧いたマイナスイオン、みんなの癒やし担当、轟はじめ、はじめます！
Hi! Pun-pun-pun! The sudden burst of negative ions, everyone's healer, Todoroki Hajime, is starting!
みなさん、こんちくわー！
Hello everyone!
紫ありがとう！
Thank you for the purple!
ついに始まりました、ReGLOSS 1st Live!
It has finally begun, ReGLOSS 1st Live!
なんと！
And what's more...
隊長は、欠席...
The captain is absent...
欠席！
Absent!
だけど、心は一緒！
But our hearts are together!
こんなにたくさんのグロッサーが集まってくれました！
And so many Grossers have gathered here for us!
すごい！もう最高な景色です、みなさん本当にありがとうございます。
Amazing! This is the absolute best view. Thank you so much, everyone.
思い思いのね、ファッションとかもね...
Your unique outfits and everything...
目で見えてね、ペンライトのグラデーションとか、ちょっとテンションが爆上がりしてしまいましたけれども...
seeing the gradient of your penlights, my excitement is just through the roof right now...
本当にありがとうございます！今日は最後まで思いっきり楽しんでまいりましょう！
Thank you so much! Let's have the absolute best time until the very end today!
そしてね、会場だけじゃなくて、配信もされております！
And it's not just at the venue, we're also being streamed!
配信のみなさんも、楽しんでますか？
Everyone on stream, are you enjoying it too?
コメント欄も...
The comment section too...
そしてそして！
And also!
韓国ではライブビューイングが実施されています！
Live viewings are being held in Korea!
안녕하세요!
Annyeonghaseyo!
라이브 뷰잉으로 보고 계시는 여러분, 재미있게 즐기고 계신가요？
Everyone watching through the live viewing, are you having fun?
おー！すごーい！
Whoa! Amazing!
やっぱり奏、すごいね！
As expected of Kanade, you're amazing!
当たり前だろ！
Of course I am!
はい、えー、ということで、早速ですが、今立っているこのステージではなく、なんと2階からの登場でございましたが、みなさんびっくりした？どうだった？
Yes! So, to start off, we actually appeared from the second floor instead of this stage we're standing on. Were you surprised? How was it?
びっくりした！
I was surprised!
オープニングから『フィーリングラデーション』、そして『バディーズ』、そして『Okey Dokey』と、3曲続けてお披露目させていただきましたが、みなさんいかがでしたでしょうか？
We performed three songs in a row starting with 'Feeling Gradation', then 'Buddies', and 'Okey Dokey'. How did everyone like it?
そしてね、みなさんもお気付きかと思いますけれども、今回のライブはバンドメンバーと一緒にお届けしています！
And as you might have noticed, we're performing today with a live band!
普段聴いているあの曲が、どんなアレンジになるのかお楽しみに！
Look forward to hearing how the songs you usually listen to will be arranged!
はい、えー、今日の感想や心に残った瞬間は、ハッシュタグ、リグロス、アンダーバー、ファーストライブでぜひポストしてください！
Yes! Please post your thoughts on today and your favorite moments using the hashtag #ReGLOSS_1stLive!
みんなの感想、後で我々見に行きますので、めちゃくちゃ楽しみです！よろしくお願いします！
We'll be checking everyone's posts later, so we're really looking forward to it! Thank you!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you!
そしてね、早速ではございますが、次の曲に行きましょうか！
And now, without further ado, shall we move on to the next song?
あ、でも待って待って待って待って！
Ah, but wait wait wait wait!
YouTubeやTikTokで見てくれているみなさん！
Everyone watching on YouTube and TikTok!
ごめんなさい！
I'm so sorry!
早いんだけど、無料チラ見せパートはなんと次の曲までとなっております！
It's early, but the free sneak peek portion is only until the next song!
えー！ やだー！
What?! No way!
まだまだ一緒に盛り上がりたいみんなは概要欄のリンクから見てください！
If you want to keep pumping things up with us, check the link in the description!
はい！うーん、みなさん！
Yes! Well, everyone!
ライブはね、まだまだ始まったばかりですよ！
The live concert has only just begun!
最後までね、一緒に最高の時間を作ろう！
Let's create the best time together until the very end!
おー！
Yeah!
Snowfall 触れる遠く
Snowfall, touching from afar
消そうと誤魔化す ノイズを鳴らす
Trying to erase it, deceiving, making noise
Slow motion
Come let me show you
おどけてみせる世界 yeah yeah yeah
This playful world, yeah yeah yeah
If the sky is falling down
If the stars have no shine
真っ白な紙の上
On a blank sheet of paper
答えをにじませる
Letting the answer blur
すべてを思うままに
Everything just as I want it
風が刻む 波のメロディ
The wind carves the melody of the waves
パンドラ パンドラ 夢を握り my heart
Pandora, Pandora, holding my dream, my heart
移ろい 色あせぬように
So that it won't fade away as times change
パンドラ パンドラ 秘密のオブジェクト
Pandora, Pandora, a secret object
Show color
Pan pan pan pan pan
Pan-pan-pan-pan-pan-pan
Show color
Pan pan pan pan pan
Pan-pan-pan-pan-pan-pan
Pandora's star
Show color
Pan pan pan pan pan
Pan-pan-pan-pan-pan-pan
研ぎ澄ます世界
A sharpened world
The silent sprout
Show color
1クールのドラマよりも長い現実
A reality longer than a single-season drama
嘘偽りなく take this pain
With no lies or falsehoods, take this pain
さあ注ぎ込んで plastic mind
Now, pour it in, plastic mind
この世に表も裏もない
In this world, there is no front or back
いつも違う表情 朧げなアイロニー
Always a different expression, a vague irony
1日を抱きしめてたいのに
Even though I want to embrace the day
静まる車窓と
The quiet car window and
揺れる暇はない 上を目指そう
No time to waver, let's aim for the top
In the world where no one's
I might of, have been kind
忍び込ませてカリソメ
Slipping in a transient thing
朽ちるまで待ちぼうけ
Waiting in vain until it decays
いずれ花になる
Eventually, it will become a flower
風が刻む 波のメロディ
The wind carves the melody of the waves
パンドラ パンドラ 夢を握り my heart
Pandora, Pandora, holding my dream, my heart
移ろい 色あせぬように
So that it won't fade away as times change
パンドラ パンドラ 秘密のオブジェクト
Pandora, Pandora, a secret object
可能性が
The possibilities are
Thrilling in the night
幾重にも重なって
Overlapping in layers
響き合うビバーチェ
Echoing together, vivace
不意にほどいた
Suddenly unwinding
その向かい風
That headwind
今こそ 切なる願い
Right now, this earnest wish
打ち鳴らせ wake up
Let it ring out, wake up!
そっと手で触れれば
If you touch gently with your hand
冬枯れの結晶
The winter-withered crystal
閉ざしてしまいそうな夜だって
Even on nights that seem about to close in
この歌声で繋ぎ止めてみせるから
Because I will keep us connected with this singing voice!
風が刻む 波のメロディ
The wind carves the melody of the waves
パンドラ パンドラ 夢を握り my heart
Pandora, Pandora, holding my dream, my heart
移ろい 色あせぬように
So that it won't fade away as times change
パンドラ パンドラ 秘密のオブジェクト
Pandora, Pandora, a secret object
Show color
Pan pan pan pan pan
Pan-pan-pan-pan-pan-pan
Show color
Pan pan pan pan pan
Pan-pan-pan-pan-pan-pan
Pandora's star
Show color
Pan pan pan pan pan
Pan-pan-pan-pan-pan-pan
研ぎ澄ます世界
A sharpened world
The silent sprout
Show color
キミとじゃなきゃだめなんだ ah
It has to be with you, ah.
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!